Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records Addendum WAG.124.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Files of the Presidents Office, 1970-1998.
  - Subseries I:C: General Files, 1970-1996.
    - AFL-CIO: Committees-Reproductive Issues, Apr 1990-Aug 1990 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO: Community Services, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - AFL-CIO: Community Services, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO: Community Services, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - AFL-CIO: Department of Professional Employees, Jan 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - AFL-CIO: Department of Professional Employees, Aug 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign, Jun 1995 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign, Jul 1995 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign, Aug 1995 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign, Sep 1995-Oct 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Articles, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Contributions, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Contribution List, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Delegates CLC, Oct 1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Delegates, International Unions, Oct 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Delegates, State Feds, Oct 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Delegates, Whip List, Oct 1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Press Releases, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Press Releases: Inauguration, Aug 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Schedules, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO: Donahue/Easterling Campaign-Sweeney Dispute, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council, 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO: Executive Council-Statements and Actions, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - AFL-CIO: Human Resources Development Institute (HRDI), 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO: HRDI, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - AFL-CIO: Industrial Union Department (IUD), Jan 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, Aug 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, Jan 1987-May 1987 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, Jun 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - AFL-CIO: IUD, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - AFL-CIO: International Affairs, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - AFL-CIO: International Affairs Committee Meeting, Aug 1987 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - AFL-CIO: International Brotherhood of Electric Workers (IBEW), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - AFL-CIO: IBEW, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - AFL-CIO: IBEW, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - AFL-CIO: International Shell Boycott Week, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX), Jan 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX), Apr 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX/XXI), 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX/XXI), 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): AFSCME and IBT, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): AFSCME, IBT, and OPEIU, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): CONTEL Telephone Operators, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): IBEW, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): IBEW, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - AFL-CIO: Jurisdictional Disputes (Article XX): Service Employees International Union (SEIU) and International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers (IFPTE), 1990 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - AFL-CIO: Meany Center for Labor Studies, Jan 1986-Jun 1986 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO: Meany Center for Labor Studies, Jul 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - AFL-CIO: Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - AFL-CIO: Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - AFL-CIO: Meany Center for Labor Studies, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - AFL-CIO: Public Employees Department, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - AFL-CIO: Public Employees Department, Jan 1987-Jul 1987 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO: Public Employees Department, Aug 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - AFL-CIO: State Councils, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - AFL-CIO: State Councils, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - AFL-CIO: State Councils, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - AFL-CIO: Trade Relations, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - AFL-CIO: 21st Constitutional Convention Credentials, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - AFL-CIO: Union Label Service and Trades Department, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - American Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T) Communications, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Apprenticeship and Employment Program, Jan 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Apprenticeship and Employment Program, Jul 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Archives, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Asian-American Free Labor Institute (AAFLI), 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Bahr Awards: Certificate, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Bahr Invitations, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Bahr Testimonial Dinner, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Broadband: Ameritech, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Business Agent Licensing, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Canadian Labor Congress, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Citizen Energy Coalition, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - CLUW, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - CLUW: Conference, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - CLUW: Convention, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - CLUW: Convention, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - CLUW: Resolution Drafts, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Collective Bargaining Forum, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Collective Bargaining Forum, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Commission on the Skills of the American Workforce, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Commission on Workforce Quality and Labor Market Efficiency, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Changing International Realities, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Committee on Equality (COE), 1986-1992 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Committee on the Future: Articles and Research (Corporation Specific), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Committee on the Future: Articles and Research (Corporation Specific), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Committee on the Future: Articles and Research (Labor and Industrial Relations), 1979-1982 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Committee on the Future: Articles and Research (Organization), 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Committee on the Future: Articles and Research (Work and Workplace), 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Committee on the Future: Bargaining Primer, Undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, Jan 1982-Mar 1982 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, Apr 1982-Jun 1982 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, Jul 1982-Sep 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, Oct 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the Future: Committee Member Correspondence, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Committee on the Future: Divestiture-AT&T, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Committee on the Future: Final Report (Draft-Chapters 1-6), Jan 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Committee on the Future: Final Report (Draft-Chapter 7-Appendices), Jan 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Committee on the Future: General, undated, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Future: General, Jan 1982-Nov 1982 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Committee on the Future: General, Dec 1982 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Committee on the Future: Goals for CWA, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Committee on the Future: Goals for CWA, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Committee on the Future: Interim Reports, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Committee on the Future: Meetings, General, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting I, Convention, Jul 30, 1981-Jul 31, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting II, Working Meeting, Oct 19, 1982-Oct 22, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting III, Dec 8, 1981-Dec 11, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting III (Dina Beaumont's Notes), Dec 8, 1981-Dec 11, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting III (Charles Savage's Notes), Dec 8, 1981-Dec 11, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting IV, Jan 19, 1982-Jan 21, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting V, Feb 23, 1982-Feb 26, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting VI, May 9, 1982-May 12, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting VII, Legislative Conference, Mar 29, 1982-Apr 2, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting VIII, Jun 14, 1982-Jun 18, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting VIII, Jun 14, 1982-Jun 18, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting IX, 44th Annual Convention, Detroit, Jul 1982 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #10, Sep 8, 1982-Sep 10, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #11, Oct 5, 1982-Oct 7, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #12, Minutes, Nov 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #12, Nov 8, 1982-Nov 12, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #13, Dec 13, 1982-Dec 16, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Future: Meeting #14 and Special Convention, Jan 1, 1983-Apr 1, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Committee on the Future: Members, Undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Committee on the Future: Public Affairs, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Committee on the Future: Questionnaires, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Committee on the Future: Special Convention, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Committee on the Future: Structure Review Committee, Reports, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Committee on the Future: Task Force, Bargaining, May 10, 1982-May 28, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Committee on the Future: Task Force, Education, Apr 18, 1982-May 14, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Committee on the Future: Task Force, General, Apr 1, 1982-Oct 1, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Committee on the Future: Task Force, Organizing, Apr 19, 1982-May 21, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Committee on the Future: Training, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Committees, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Committees: Constitution Committee, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Committees: Constitution Committee, Members, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Committees: National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador, 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Committees: National Planning Association, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Committees: National Planning Association, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Committees: Urban Affairs, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Communications Systems Industry (CSI), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - CWA General Counsel, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - CWA Mastercard Program, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - CWA Mastercard Program, Jan 1987-Apr 1987 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - CWA Mastercard Program, May 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - CWA Mastercard Program, Jul 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - CWA Task Force, 1991-1993 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Community Services, Apr 1986-May 1986 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Community Services, Jun 1986-Aug 1986 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Community Services, Sep 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Community Services, Jan 1987-May 1987 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Community Services, Jun 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Community Services, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Community Services, Jun 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Conferences, 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Conferences, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Conferences, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Conferences, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Conferences, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Conferences, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Conferences, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Conferences, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Conferences I, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Conferences II, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Conferences, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Conferences, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Consumer Affairs, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Consumer Affairs, Apr 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Contributions, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Contributions, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Contributions, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Contributions, Jun 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Convention: Action/Reading, Dina Beaumont, Jan 1986-Mar 1986 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Convention: Action/Reading, Dina Beaumont, Jun 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Convention: Action/Reading, Dina Beaumont, Oct 1986 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Conventions: 43rd and 44th Annual Conventions, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Conventions: 45th and 46th Annual Convention, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Conventions: 47th Annual Convention, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Conventions: 48th and 49th Annual Convention, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Conventions: 50th Annual Convention, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Conventions: 52nd and 53rd Annual Convention, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Conventions: 54th Annual Convention, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Conventions: 55th Annual Convention, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Daily News Summary, Jan 1986-Feb 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Daily News Summary, Mar 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Daily News Summary, Apr 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Daily News Summary, May 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Daily News Summary, Jun 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Daily News Summary, Jul 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Daily News Summary, Aug 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Daily News Summary, Oct 1986-Nov 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Daily News Summary, Dec 1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Daily News Summary, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Daily News Summary, Mar 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Daily News Summary, Apr 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Daily News Summary, May 1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Daily News Summary, Jun 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Daily News Summary, Jul 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Daily News Summary, Sep 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Daily News Summary, Oct 1987 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Daily News Summary, Nov 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Daily News Summary, Jan 1988 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Daily News Summary, Feb 1988 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Daily News Summary, Mar 1, 1988-Mar 16, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Daily News Summary, Mar 17, 1988-Mar 31, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Daily News Summary, Apr 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Decertification, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Defense Fund, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Development and Research, Jan 13, 1986-Jan 17, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Development and Research, Jan 17, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Development and Research, Jan 17, 1986-Jan 21, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Development and Research, Jan 28, 1986-Jan 31, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Development and Research, Feb 3, 1986-Feb 5, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Development and Research, Feb 6, 1986-Feb 13, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Development and Research, Feb 14, 1986-Feb 18, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Development and Research, Feb 18, 1986-Feb 20, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Development and Research, Feb 21, 1986-Feb 27, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Development and Research, Feb 28, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Development and Research, Mar 3, 1986-Mar 12, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Development and Research, Mar 13, 1986-Mar 20, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Development and Research, Mar 21, 1986-Mar 26, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Development and Research, Mar 27, 1986-Mar 31, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Development and Research, Apr 1, 1986-Apr 3, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Development and Research, Apr 4, 1986-Apr 10, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Development and Research, Apr 11, 1986-Apr 30, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Development and Research, May 1, 1986-May 12, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Development and Research, May 13, 1986-May 15, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Development and Research, May 15, 1986-May 17, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Development and Research, Jun 1986 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Development and Research, Jul 1986 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Development and Research, Aug 1, 1986-Aug 20, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Development and Research, Aug 22, 1986-Aug 29, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Development and Research, Sep 3, 1986-Sep 17, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Development and Research, Sep 18, 1986-Sep 22, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Development and Research, Sep 23, 1986-Sep 30, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Development and Research, Oct 1, 1986-Oct 17, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Development and Research, Oct 20, 1986-Oct 31, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Development and Research, Nov 3, 1986-Nov 12, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Development and Research, Nov 13, 1986-Nov 26, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Development and Research, Dec 1, 1986-Dec 18, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Development and Research, Dec 19, 1986-Dec 31, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Development and Research, Jan 5, 1987-Jan 8, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Development and Research, Jan 9, 1987-Jan 30, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Development and Research, Feb 2, 1987-Feb 9, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Development and Research, Feb 10, 1987-Feb 27, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Development and Research, Mar 2, 1987-Mar 19, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Development and Research, Mar 20, 1987-Mar 31, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Development and Research, Apr 2, 1987-Apr 13, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Development and Research, Apr 14, 1987-Apr 22, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Development and Research, Apr 23, 1987-Apr 30, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Development and Research, May 1, 1987-May 8, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Development and Research, May 19, 1987-May 29, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Development and Research, Jun 1, 1987-Jun 11, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Development and Research, Jun 12, 1987-Jun 30, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Development and Research, Jul 1, 1987-Jul 13, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Development and Research, Jul 14, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Development and Research, Jul 14, 1987-Jul 31, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Development and Research, Aug 3, 1987-Aug 28, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Development and Research, Sep 1987 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Development and Research, Oct 1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Development and Research, Nov 1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Development and Research, Dec 1987 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Development and Research, Jan 1988-Feb 1988 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Development and Research, Mar 1988-Apr 1988 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Development and Research, May 1988-Jun 1988 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Development and Research, Jul 1988-Aug 1988 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Development and Research, Sep 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Disability: Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), 1993 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Dues, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Economic Policy Council, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Economic Policy Institute, 1986-1988 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Economic Policy Institute, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Education, Jan 1986-Feb 1986 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Education, Mar 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Education, Aug 1986-Sep 1986 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Education, Oct 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Education, Jan 1987-Feb 1987 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Education, Mar 1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Education, Apr 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Education, May 1987-Jul 1987 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Education, Aug 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Education, Sep 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Education, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Education, Jun 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Education, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Education, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Education, 1993-1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Education, 1995-1996 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Education: Choices Program, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Jan 1986-Feb 1986 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Mar 1986-Jul 1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Aug 1986-Dec 1986 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Jan 1987-Mar 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Apr 1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, May 1987-Jun 1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Jul 1987-Nov 1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Jan 1988-Mar 1988 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Education: Colleges, Universities and Schools, Apr 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Education: CWA Apprenticeship and Employment Program, Jan 1988-Apr 1988 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Education: CWA Apprenticeship and Employment Program, May 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Education: CWA Apprenticeship and Employment Program, Aug 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Education: Conferences, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Education: Correspondence re: Signed Photos of National Leaders, Feb 1988-Oct 1988 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Education: Educational Material, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Education: Growth and Development, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Education: Posters and Bulletins, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Education: Posters and Bulletins, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Education: Week-Long Schools, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Education: Week-Long Schools, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Elections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Elections: Challenges, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 36)